const Family = [
	{
		questionText: 'Who said - Family is a social group that is charaterised by commom residence, economic coop,....',
		ans: ['George Murdock'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who said - Family is a biological unit of H,W, childeren',
		ans: ['Eliott & Merrill'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who said family is group of maternal relations, duties of parent hoods, reciprocal relationship b/w parents and childrens',
		ans: ['R.H Lowiee'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Archy means',
		ans: ['Ownership'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Potestal means',
		ans: ['Power'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Hindu marriage act',
		ans: ['1955'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Muslim women (protection on Right on Marriage) Act',
		ans: ['2019'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Proctection of women from domestic violence act',
		ans: ['2005'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Ogburn & Nimkoff divided the family into ______ categories',
		ans: ['6'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Reed divided family into ______ categories  ',
		ans: ['4'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Duvall has classified ______ stages of family life cycle',
		ans: [''],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is conjugal family',
		ans: ['relations b/w individuals is through  marriage'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'what is Consangunie family',
		ans: ['relations b/w individuals is through common ancestorys'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Marriage is a bundle of Rights',
		ans: ['Leach'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Marriage is a contract for production and maintanance of childeren',
		ans: ['Malinowski'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Marriage is perminant bond',
		ans: ['Lowie'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Edmund & Majumder explains ______ rights performed by marriage',
		ans: ['10'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'child familiarity theory',
		ans: ['Westermarck'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Family Disruption Thoery',
		ans: ['Malinowski'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Psycho analytical Theory',
		ans: ['Sigmund Freud'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Cooperation Thoery',
		ans: ['EB Taylor'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Indian Divorce act',
		ans: ['1869'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Term Kin was coined by ?',
		ans: ['Andrew Lang & F.G. Frazer'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The book "Primitive Marriage" is written by?',
		ans: ['Mc Lenman'],
	},
	{
		questionText: '	Who said " The social relationship deriving from blood ties and marriage are reffered as KINGSHIP"',
		ans: ['Aber Chrombie'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'who used the term Kinship and in which book',
		ans: ['Sir Henry Maine in Ancient Law'],
	},
	{
		questionText: '_______ said primary kins has ____-',
		ans: ['Dr Dubey', '8'],
	},
	{
		questionText: '2ndary kinship contains____',
		ans: ['33'],
	},
	{
		questionText: '_______ said Teritary kinship constain ____',
		ans: ['Murdock', '151'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is Agnate',
		ans: ['Whose common Ancestor is male '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is Uterine',
		ans: ['Whose common Anscestor is Female'],
	},
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },

];

export default Family;
